guitarhero.com 2015-11-05

# Activision | Privacy Policy

**Activision uses "Cookies" to tailor content, marketing, and improve and adjust user experience. To find out more about "Cookies", and options available to manage them, pleaseclick here** **. By using this Activision online property, you consent to our use of "Cookies".**

**Welcome to Activision's Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 17, 2015.**

This Privacy Policy:

  * explains how Activision collects, stores, uses, and may transfer or disclose your **Information;**
  * applies to all Activision websites, products and services (" **Activision Properties** ") **** that post or link to it.

By using the Activision Properties you agree, and consent, to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use any Activision Properties.

**Summary, Scope & Changes** : Everyday, millions of people worldwide use and enjoy Activision Properties. We appreciate your trust of our products and services. In order to provide you with great games and make them better, Activision may collect both personal information and non-personal information (collectively, " **Information** "). We take care of how Information related to you is processed and used.

Whenever you use an Activision Property we may:

  * collect, process, and combine data such as your age, gender, interests, name, email address, gameplay, marketing preferences, customer service, and device-related information (like your IP address)
  * contact you from time to time to request your opinion about Activision Properties, provide you with customer service, and other services you have requested
  * use web beacons, cookies and similar technologies, or flash technology on Activision Properties or in email messages to tailor content, marketing and improve and adjust user experiences
  * disclose Information to Activision group companies
  * share Information with suppliers and partners in order to provide you with goods or services you have requested or online advertising selected by us. We do not share Information with third parties to use for their own direct marketing purposes without your agreement
  * collect, process and store Information on servers in the United States or other countries where Activision group companies or suppliers maintain facilities or business operations. Activision takes reasonable measures to safeguard your privacy rights in accordance with this Privacy Policy

Click here for details Hide details

**Scope** : This Privacy Policy applies only to those Activision Properties that post, reference, or link to it, including:

  * Activision Websites, online products and services
  * Activision Apps
  * Activision Console Video Games

This Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites or online properties to which Activision Properties may link, and you accept Activision is not responsible for the security or privacy practices of any such third party websites or properties.

**Changes:** We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy we will provide notice in our Privacy Policy as posted. Your continued use of an Activision Property will signify your acceptance of any changes. If you do not agree to any changes, you must stop using the Activision Property. The applicable terms of service for the Activision Property will tell you options available to terminate any account you may have.

**ESRB** :  
This Privacy Policy and the ESRB certification seals shown on our websites confirm that Activision is a licensee and participating member in the [Entertainment Software Rating Board's (" **ESRB** ") Privacy Certified Program](http://www.esrb.org/privacy/faq.jsp). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and ESRB Privacy Certified has reviewed and certified that we meet established online information collection and use practices on all Activision Properties where this Privacy Policy is posted.

Click here for details Hide details

As part of the ESRB Privacy Certified Program, we are subject to frequent audits of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB.

Whenever you visit a website that displays the ESRB Privacy Certified certification seal, you may request information about:

  * Whether a company uses cookies, tracks IP Addresses or uses other passive means to collect information;
  * Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information and how will it be used;
  * With whom, if anyone, will your personal information be shared;
  * What choices you have with regard to the use of your personal information;
  * How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company collects and maintains;
  * Whether and how information is collected from children under 13;
  * How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity;
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints.

_DISCLAIMER: Although ESRB Privacy Certified does not monitor non-English Activision Properties, Activision makes all best efforts to ensure that non-English Properties adhere to applicable data collection guidance and principles set forth by ESRB Privacy Certified, including adherence to the EU Directive._

If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact the ESRB at:

_http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp_

ESRB  
Attn: Privacy Certified Program  
420 Lexington Ave, Suite 2024  
New York, NY 10170  
_privacy@esrb.org_

**Information We Collect and How We Use It** : We collect Information from you and other sources, and we use that Information to operate, personalize, and improve our Activision Properties, and to send you marketing messages or personalized advertising.

Click here for details Hide details

**Information Provided By You** : Activision collects Information from you when you: (1) open an Activision account with an Activision Property; (2) use an Activision Property; (3) participate in Activision sweepstakes, contests and promotions; (4) use Activision customer service; (5) choose to receive newsletters on products and services, receive marketing emails, and/or participate in surveys; (6) buy Activision services or products online; (7) apply for job openings; (8) use "send-a-friend" functionality; (9) allow sharing through Social Media.

1\. Account Registration

Activision collects certain personal information from you when you register with an Activision Property, such as your name, address, email address, and phone number. Unfortunately, as of September 1st, 2015, we will no longer be able to offer Activision accounts to Russian based consumers.

2\. Use an Activision Property

When you visit or use Activision Properties we may collect Information about your use of those Activision Properties, such as pages visited, browser type and language, your IP address, the website you came from, gameplay data, purchase histories, and Social Media data. We may use Cookies or similar technologies to do this. See the Cookies section below for more details.

3\. Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions

When Activision runs contests or promotions on Activision Properties we may collect certain personal information from participants such as their name, address, postal code, email address, phone number, age and/or date of birth. That information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise stated in the contest terms or rules.

4\. Customer Service

In order to provide you with customer service, Activision may collect personal information from you including your name, email address, and birth date, together with details of your customer service issue and its resolution.

5\. Receive newsletters on products and services, receive marketing emails, and/or participate in surveys

Activision may offer you the ability to receive newsletters periodically by email about our services and products. At any time, you can manage your preferences from your account settings and stop receiving further newsletters by unsubscribing from the link in the footer of each email we send to you.

You also may subscribe to marketing campaigns run by ourselves or by third parties, only if you opt-in to it.

We may, from time to time, send you surveys in order to improve player experience with our games.

6\. Buy Activision services or products online

If you buy Activision services or products (such as digital content) online you may be required to provide credit card and billing information to one of our third-party vendors in order to complete a purchase. At the time of purchase, you may also have the option to provide personal information to Activision for the purpose of sending you additional information or offers.

7\. Résumés

For selected job postings, you may send us your résumé or other relevant information online. Personal information collected in association with job postings will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings.

8\. Send-a-Friend

From time to time, Activision may offer you the ability to email or message friends or family by using our "send-a-friend" tool. We delete both sender and recipient email addresses after sending the message. In using our "send-a-friend" tool, you confirm that you and the recipient know each other and that you have their consent to send them an email.

9\. Social Media

You can interact with some Activision Properties through social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter (or social media plug-ins and applications) (" **Social Media** "). When you interact with Activision through Social Media you authorize us to access Information - solely in accordance with your Social Media privacy settings - from your Social Media account (e.g., name, email address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the 'likes' you make) to tailor content, marketing, and improve and adjust user experience relating to Activision Properties. We may also obtain other Information from your interaction with our content (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on). When you provide Information from your Social Media account, it can help us to (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our websites (and/or applications), and (3) contact you in accordance with applicable marketing preferences through Social Media or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. When you post personal information publicly through Activision Properties, or on Social Media, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the personal information by third parties. Social Media sites and applications may also place their own cookies on your device (see our Cookies section below for more details) and will often allow you to control what data you share by changing your privacy settings with that Social Media site or application. For more information about how your Social Media sites and applications use and protect your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use. You agree that Activision shall not be liable for the use by Social Media sites and applications of Information you have supplied to them.

**Information Provided By Other Sources:** We may also obtain Information about you from other sources, such as Social Media, network advertising companies, and data brokers, and combine that information with Information we have collected from or about you. For example, we may obtain online network advertising data derived from cookies (see our Cookies section below for more details); name and postal address; age; your interests and hobbies; consumer and market research data; online and in-store purchase behavior; and publicly observed or shared data, such as Social Media, blogs, videos, internet postings, and user generated content. We only collect Information from other sources where those sources have confirmed to us they are legally entitled to share it.

**How We Use Information** :  
Activision collects and may combine Information provided by you and other sources to tailor content, marketing, and improve and adjust user experiences on Activision Properties and third party online properties. Please see the **Choices** section below for details of the choices you have over how we use Information.

**How We Treat Children’s Information** : Activision does not knowingly collect or store any personally identifiable information such as name, address, or email address from children under 13. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, phone numbers, or other personal information without parental permission, when online. Activision also recommends that parents familiarize themselves with parental controls available on consoles, mobile telephones, tablets and other devices they provide to their child and accompany their child if aged under 13 years of age when online. Parents should contact Activision immediately if they have any concerns that we have unintentionally collected personal information about their child. Please see the **Contacting Us** section below for further details.

**Your Choices:** You have choices over

  * the Information provided by you
  * the Information provided by other sources
  * how that Information is used

Click here for details Hide details

**Your Choices about Information Provided By You** : If you do not want to provide Activision with personal information that is requested directly by us then you can choose not to provide it. Please note that if you choose not to provide us with personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the relevant Activision product or service that you want. For example, without providing personal information requested directly by us, you will not be able to (1) open an Activision account with an Activision Property; (2) use an Activision Property; (3) participate in Activision sweepstakes, contests and promotions; (4) use Activision customer service; (5) choose to receive newsletters on products and services, receive marketing emails, and/or participate in surveys; (6) buy Activision services or products online; (7) apply for job openings; (8) use "send-a-friend" functionality; (9) allow sharing through Social Media.

Additionally, with respect to device-related information you can choose whether or not you want to allow certain cookies (and similar technology) to collect information about your use of Activision Properties, and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns (see our Cookies section below).

**Your Choices about Information Provided by Others:** You may be able to control how third parties collect and share your Information by changing your preferences or opting out of collection directly with those third parties. Before disclosing Information to third parties, we recommend you check their respective privacy policies for further details.

Additionally, with respect to device-related information you can choose whether or not you want to allow certain cookies (and similar technology) to collect information about your use of third party online properties, and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns (see our Cookies section below).

**Your Choices About Activision Using Your Information:** You can exercise choices over how Activision uses your personal information and update your preferences at any time:

  * to remove yourself from individual contests or promotions, or from receiving email marketing or newsletters from Activision, simply click the unsubscribe link in the email or access your account from _http://www.activision.com/_ and edit/delete your email marketing preferences. You will need your password to access your account.
  * to disable selected Cookies from collecting information relating to the effectiveness of advertising campaigns or analytics data and from serving you with personalized advertising on Activision Properties or third party properties please see our Cookies section.

If you do not want Activision to reply to your customer support inquiry, you may opt-out from receiving a response by contacting us at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com), or by regular mail: for US, Canadian, and Mexican residents at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy; and for the rest of the world at: Activision Blizzard UK Limited, Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK, ATTN: International Legal, Privacy.

If you opt-out of email marketing communications from us, please note we may still contact you occasionally about the status of your account, such as to inform you that your account may be expiring, or other service related information.

**Sharing Information:** Activision shares Information with

  * Vendors engaged by Activision to provide goods and/or services on behalf of Activision
  * other third parties to provide goods or services you have requested
  * law enforcement or other government officials
  * if required to do so by law

Please note that any information, including personally identifiable information that you reveal in a bulletin board, message board, chat room, or other public forum is publicly viewable.

Click here for details Hide details

**Vendors:** Vendors provide goods and services (for example, billing, customer services support, consultancy, information technology hardware and software) to Activision in order to support, operate and develop the Activision Properties and to deliver marketing communications on our behalf. We do not share Information with vendors to use for their own direct marketing purposes without your agreement.

**Third Parties:** Other third parties may need your Information in order to provide goods and/or services you have requested. For example, to deliver Activision digital content you have purchased through your games console, mobile phone, or tablet.

**Law:** You agree we may disclose your Information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. We may review your gameplay, communications, and other account information in order to investigate allegations of cheating, hacking or any other breach or alleged breach of any applicable Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy and disclose your personal information, including communications, to our legal advisors, consultants and law enforcement or other government officials.

Separately, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Activision's customer information including Information and communications may be transferred to our successor or assign.

**Security:** Activision takes a range of security measures designed to help protect your personal information. However, complete online and offline security can never be guaranteed, so you should always take care when sharing your information online.

Click here for details Hide details

Activision takes a range of security measures designed to protect your personal information and keep it confidential (unless it is non-confidential by nature, for example, publicly-available information like user generated content, leaderboard rankings, and scores, etc.) and in its original form, in other words, free from any alteration. In addition, we request Vendors who process personal information on our behalf to themselves take a range of security measures designed to help protect your personal information. However, the internet by its nature is not a secure environment and the nature of security risks is constantly evolving, as are the technical and organizational industry standards relating to management of those risks. The complete security of any personal information collected, stored or used by us or our Vendors cannot therefore be guaranteed.

We will notify users of a data breach involving unencrypted personal information by email or by posting a notice on the affected website.

**Accessing Information:** You can access, update, or delete your personally identifiable information in any of your Activision accounts at any time.

Click here for details Hide details

If for any reason you wish to view, correct, or delete personally identifiable information collected about you, simply access your Activision account through <https://www.activision.com/> or other product or service as applicable and edit/delete your information as necessary. You will need your password to access your personal account. You may also send us an email asking us to delete your account at [removeaccount@activision.com](mailto:removeaccount@activision.com). In the alternative, you may write to us: for US, Canadian, and Mexican residents at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy; and for the rest of the world at: Activision Blizzard UK Limited, Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK, ATTN: International Legal, Privacy. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. Residual copies of information that have been deleted from your account may remain in our backup systems for up to 30 days. We may still retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements; in this case, your personal information will be blocked from use for any other purpose.

**Contacting Us:** If you are a visitor to Activision Properties from the US, Canada or Mexico the information you submit to the Activision Properties is controlled by Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405, USA.

If you are visitor to Activision Properties from another country, then the information you submit is controlled by Activision Blizzard UK Limited of Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK. Activision Blizzard UK Limited is registered as data controller with the UK Information Commissioner's Office with registration number Z1095341.

Click here for details Hide details

Visitors from the US, Canada or Mexico can send us an email at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com), or write to us at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy, or call Privacy Team/Privacy Policy, ph. +1 310 255 2000.

Visitors from another country can send us an email at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com), or write to us at: Activision Blizzard UK Limited of Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK.

You may also contact the ESRB if you have a question or complaint that has not been resolved to your satisfaction. Please see the **ESRB** section at the top of this Privacy Policy for further details.

**Important Notices:** For privacy related information applicable to users who are California residents or based outside the US please see below.

Please note your use of this Activision website, product or service is also subject to the terms of the Activision Product License & Service Agreement available [here](http://cmsauthor.activision.com/legal/terms-of-use).

**California Privacy Rights** : Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an email to _privacy@activision.com_ , or write us at : Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy. We will be happy to honor your request.

**California Privacy Rights for Minor Users:** Since January 1, 2015, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you, if you are a California resident under the age of 18, to view, correct, or delete information provided by you or publicly posted by you, by simply accessing your Activision account through <http://www.activision.com/> or other product or service as applicable and editing/deleting your information as necessary. You will need your password to access your personal account. You may also send us an email asking us to delete certain posted content at privacy@activision.com. In the alternative, you may write to us at Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy.

We will be happy to review, update or remove information and/or content as appropriate. Residual copies of information and/or content that have been deleted from your account and/or Activision Properties may remain in our backup systems for up to 30 days. We may still retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements; in this case, your personal information will be blocked from use for any other purpose.

**Disclosure to Users Outside the US** : In addition, if you are a visitor to our websites or other online products and services from outside the U.S., the personal information you provide may be collected, processed and stored directly on, or transferred to, servers in the United States or other countries where Activision group companies or Vendors maintain facilities or business operations.

Information collected with the European Economic Area and Switzerland may be transferred to the United States. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree such international transfers of your Information.

No matter where the Information is located, Activision takes all commercial reasonable measures to safeguard your privacy rights in accordance with this Privacy Policy If you do not agree to the collection, processing, storage and transfer of your information, please do not provide your information when requested and stop using our websites and other online products and services.

**Cookies & Do Not Track:** What are Cookies, and how does Activision use Cookies, track IP addresses, and other persistent identifiers and passive means to collect information?

Activision uses Cookies and/or similar technologies on Activision Properties. A "Cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that many websites and other online products and services often store on a user's computer or device in order to identify it and associate activity with it.

When visiting Activision Properties you may have options to enable or disallow Cookies. We use Cookies to optimize your visit, make your browsing and/or user experience as effective as possible, and let you know about offers and features that we think will interest you. This means that if you disallow cookies, your use of Activision Properties may be impaired.

Depending on the Activision Property you are using, and the country you are based in, cookies may be set on your computer or device by either:

  * Activision - to recognize and associate activity with your computer or device when it visits an Activision Property. Activision cookies cannot be used to recognize or associate activity with your computer or device when it visits other, third party websites or online properties.
  * Third Parties - to enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through Activision Properties or other online properties (e.g. advertising and analytics). The third parties that set these cookies may be able to recognize your computer or device both when it visits Activision Properties or other online properties that use the third party's features and functionality

Click here for details Hide details

**Types Of Cookies:** There are four categories of Cookies:

  * _Necessary Cookies_

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around websites or online properties and use their features, such as accessing secure areas of a website. Without these cookies, Activision cannot provide services you have asked for, like secure login areas.

  * _Performance (or Analytics) Cookies_

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website or online property, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information about the actual identity (e.g., first and last name) of a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. They are only used to improve how a website or other online property works. We generally contract with independent research and measurement companies, such as Google Analytics, to provide these services on our behalf and these third parties also have their own privacy policies.

  * _Functionality Cookies_

These cookies allow the website or online property to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personalized features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

  * _Advertising Cookies_

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They also help limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website or online property operator's permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization. In certain countries Activision may partner with third party online advertising and analytics companies to tailor and deliver advertisements, products, services, and promotions on Activision Properties, as well as other online properties which we do not control. To help select the ads of greatest interest to you, these companies may use cookies, Flash technology, and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic data (e.g., gender, occupation, etc.), aggregated information, search keywords, geo-location, and device-related data (for example, browser type, language, IP address, time/date) to select advertisements that are more relevant to your interests, to better personalize the experience for you and tailor advertisements. In some instances, third-parties may also use cookies or similar technologies to collect anonymized or device-related information about your visits to Activision Properties in order to provide third party advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

To learn more about Advertising Cookies visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) at _http://networkadvertising.org_ or _http://youronlinechoices.com_.

Activision may use and share anonymized or aggregated information obtained from cookies with third parties such as Vendors or advertising partners. An example of the use of such information would be creating interest categories or segments based on region, gaming preferences, or a combination. We may also share personal and non-personally identifiable information obtained from cookies with third parties such as Vendors or advertising networks in order to permit them to provide services on our behalf or to partner with us in selecting and serving advertisements for us or our advertising partners.

**Social Network Sites**

If you have signed in to a social networking site, such as Facebook, it may have set a cookie on your device which recognizes you when you view content on our websites and other online properties. These cookies allow you to share content across social media via the use of sharing settings. See your social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy for details. For additional details, please see the Social Media references in the Information We Collect And How We Use It and Your Choices sections above.

**Do Not Track**

California Business and Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) permits our customers who are California residents to be informed as to how Activision responds to Web browser "Do Not Track" settings. As Do Not Track is a standard that is currently being developed, Activision does not take actions to respond to Do Not Track settings, and instead we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy.

**More Information**

If you would like to find out more about cookies you may find the following link useful:

_http://www.allaboutcookies.org/_

_If you would like to find out more about Do Not Track you may find the following link useful:_

http://www.allaboutdnt.com/

**Managing Cookies & Do Not Track Options:** You can review your options to manage cookies by:

  * clicking on the opt out links provided in the Cookie List below
  * opening the "Help" menu on the browser menu bar. Most browsers will tell you how you can disable or delete cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.
  * visiting _http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp_ and/or _http://youronlinechoices.com_ for choices to opt out of advertising

If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of our websites and other products and services (including sign in).

**Permission to Use Cookies:** By using Activision Properties you agree, and we will assume you consent, to receive cookies unless you manage your cookie choices by one of the means set out above.

Please also note that the use of information obtained by third party providers listed in Appendix 1 through cookies placed by them is also subject to their own privacy policies. Information collected by cookies may be associated with your registration account or user profile.

**Flash cookies, web beacons, IP addresses:** Adobe Flash Player is an application that allows sites to deploy dynamic web content. Adobe Flash and similar applications use technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage in ways that are similar to browser cookies, but are managed through a different interface than your web browser. You can access your Flash management tools from _http://www.adobe.com/_ directly to manage your cookie settings. From time to time, we may use web beacons (or clear GIFs) on our websites or other online properties or include them in the email messages we send you. Web beacons (also known as "web bugs") are small strings of code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. We use web beacons for many purposes, including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and email auditing and reporting, and personalization. We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

**Cookies List:** Your Activision Property may contain, but is not limited to, the following third party Performance (or Analytics) and Advertising cookies. Please follow the links below for details of the Privacy Policies and Opt Out Choices offered by these third parties. Please also see the Cookies section above for further options available to manage cookies.

**Online Property**

| 

**Third Party Cookies**

| 

**Third Party Privacy Policies and Opt Out Choices**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Websites**

| 

Add This

| 

<http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>

<http://www.addthis.com/advertising-choices>  
  
  | 

Adobe Test & Target

| 

<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/analytics.html>

<https://microsite.omniture.com/t2/help/en_US/tnt/help/#Add_an_OptOut_Link>

<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
  | 

Comscore

| 

<http://www.comscore.com/About_comScore/Privacy_Policy>

<http://www.sitestat.com/>  
  
  | 

Cross Pixel Media

| 

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
  
  | 

Data Logix

| 

<https://www.datalogix.com/privacy/>  
  
  | 

Google Analytics

| 

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
  
  | 

Sizmek

| 

<http://www.sizmek.com/about-us/privacy>  
  
  | 

Media6 Degrees

| 

<http://m6d.com/privacy/privacy-policy/>  
  
  | 

ScoreCard Research

| 

<http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx>  
  
  | 

ShareThis

| 

<http://sharethis.com/privacy>  
  
  | 

Tribal Fusion

| 

<http://www.exponential.com/about-us/privacy.html>  
  
  | 

Videology

| 

<http://www.videologygroup.com/index.php/en/menu-privacy-policy.html>  
  
| 

Accuen

| 

<http://www.accuenmedia.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Kenshoo

| 

<http://kenshoo.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Doubleclick

| 

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
  
| 

Xaxis

| 

<http://www.xaxis.com/static/view/privacy-policy>  
  
| 

Google Adwords

| 

<https://www.google.com/intl/en-US/policies/privacy/>  
  
| 

Facebook Exchange

| 

<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
  
**Apps for mobile phones and tablets**

| 

Swrve

| 

<http://swrve.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
  | 

Flurry

| 

<http://www.flurry.com/user-opt-out.html>  
  
  | 

Kochava

| 

<http://kochava.com/privacy/>  
  
| 

Tubemogul

| 

<http://www.tubemogul.com/compliance/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Upsight

| 

<http://www.upsight.com/pricing/privacy-policy/>
